let questions = [
    { 
      id: '0',
      question: 'The occipital area of the skull is located in what part of the skull?',
      option1: 'Front',
      option2: 'Back',
      option3: 'Top',
      answer: 'Back',
    },
    {
      id: '1',
      question: 'The biceps femoris muscle is located in what part of the body?',
      option1: 'Shoulder', 
      option2: 'Arm',
      option3: 'Leg',
      answer: 'Leg',
    },
    {
      id: '2',
      question: 'The elbow is an example of what type of joint?',
      option1: 'Pivot joint',
      option2: 'Hinge joint',
      option3: 'Ball and Socket joint',
      answer: 'Hinge joint',
    },
     { 
      id: '3',
      question: 'The muscles located at the front of the thigh are known as what?',
      option1: 'Adductors', 
      option2: 'Hamstrings', 
      option3: 'Quadriceps',
      answer: 'Quadriceps',
     },
     {
      id: '4',
      question: 'The C1 vertebra is called?',
      option1: 'Atlas',
      option2: 'Axis',
      option3: 'Amino',
      answer: 'Atlas'
     }, 
     {
      id: '5',
      question: 'The three bones that form the ankle are the fibula, tibia and which other bone?',
      option1: 'Talus',
      option2: 'Calcaneous',
      option3: 'Cuboid',
      answer: 'Talus',
     },
     {
      id: '6',
      question: 'Which vessel returns unoxygenated blood to the lungs?',
      option1: 'Aorta',
      option2: 'Pulmonary artery',
      option3: 'Pulmonary vein',
      answer: 'Pulmonary artery'
     }, 
    {
      id: '7',
      question: 'Ligaments and Tendons are composed of what type of tissue?',
      option1: 'Epithelial',
      option2: 'Adipose',
      option3: 'Connective',
      answer: 'Connective',
      },
    {
      id: '8',
      question: 'The anatomical term for the head is?',
      option1: 'Cephalic',
      option2: 'Cervical',
      option3: 'Thoracic',
      answer: 'Cephalic',
       }, 
    {
      id: '9',
      question: 'Mastication is the term for what?',
      option1: 'Chewing',
      option2: 'Snoring',
      option3: 'Swallowing',
      answer: 'Chewing'
        }  
      ];

      let questionContainer = document.getElementById('question-area');
      let startButton = document.getElementById('start-button');
      let nextButton = document.getElementById('next-q');

      console.log(questionContainer);
      console.log(questions);

